[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 0, "question": "Is this the angriest man in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 1, "answer": "These poor bankers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "You've calmed down since our last encounter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "No, I haven't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "I mean what are you like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Well, you actually have seen me backstage here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "Do you ever wish you hadn't decided to embark on this crazy second life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last 30 years"], "PERSON": ["Obama", "Obama", "Franklin Roosevelt"]}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", ":", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "IN", ":", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "What did you make of the speech?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "I think that this is the Obama that I voted for, and I think the majority of people who voted for him voted for this Obama that -- today he referenced Franklin Roosevelt and that -- and that we have to get out of this mentality we've been in for the last 30 years, as he said, where it's the sort of you're on your own economy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 121, "question": "What are you referencing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "Of where I think you're wrong about the comparison --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "The message has not got through, has it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "Well, this is a problem.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 199, "question": "But that's not true, though, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "When I -- when I was of college age --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "Do you believe that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "Yes, they're -- let me tell you right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "What is the answer then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "Well, the answer is reality.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "DT", ":", "NN", "POS", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "How's that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "Let's turn to the -- let's turn to the real villains.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "Well, 25 percent is a lot of people, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["25 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "The bailouts and so on, should those people who did deliberately really spend beyond their means, should they be bailed out in the way that you're talking about with these foreclosures?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "MD", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "Isn't that -- wouldn't that be the decent thing to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", ":", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "No, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "What would be wrong with asking for a special prosecutor to investigate how that crash happened in first place?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "IN", "JJ", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "I agree with you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "Isn't it right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "-- is an outrage.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Cobb County", "Congress"], "LOCATION": ["Georgia"]}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "So you and Newt then best buddies?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "RB", "JJS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "Well, yes, I went down to Cobb County, Georgia, which he represented in Congress.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Newt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Well, I have more footage.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "Do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PDT", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "Yes, I have all the outtakes that didn't make it on the air.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "MD", "VB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "Is it good stuff?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "There might be, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Are you planning to release this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "I'm not planning on him being the nominee.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RBR", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "I can't believe he's going to -- how long -- what is the shelf life of a Republican candidate in the number one position this year?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", ":", "WRB", "JJ", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "Maybe like a bottle of Chateau (INAUDIBLE), he just got better with age.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "He's intelligent?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "He's a smart guy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "But does anything that he said resonate as potentially truthful?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "Why is he the front-runner?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "Because it's like last comic standing on your other network that you used to -- it is going to be like the last one standing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Michigan"]}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", ",", "WP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "Are you referring to Mr. Romney?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "Yes, I would be referring to him, who, by the way, was born in my state of Michigan.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "Actually that is probably true, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "It is true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNPS", "CC", "RB", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "What is the reality about you and your wealth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "I think Republicans and right wingers, they blow me up into this kind of really mythical, scary character.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "How much have your movies grossed in total?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "I don't have the number right off hand.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "Half a billion dollars?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["billion dollars"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "If you were to leave tomorrow, you'd presumably leave a good old pile, wouldn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 577, "question": "Presumably you don't think everyone in the one percent is evil, do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 578, "answer": "Absolutely not, no, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "Can I have their names, please?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "You know there are good ones.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "I'm going to do that, but I'm not going to demonize you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "I think that's the way he talked for the first three years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 643, "question": "If you're carving up Republican responsibility, Democrat and the American public, Wall Street, how would you do it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "Well, look --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "CC", "DT", "NNPS", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "NNPS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 652, "question": "That's why I asked you to do a proper pie chart, because I don't think that's fair, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "POS", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 653, "answer": "Well, it's only fair in the sense that you have to understand that the Republicans and the Democrats -- and it's mostly Republican, but Democrats have colluded over the years with this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 667, "question": "-- for the Republican nominee, what do you think of that?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 668, "answer": "Good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 670, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 671, "answer": "Well, one, comedy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"], "LOCATION": ["Washington"]}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "''", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RBR", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "So what is your theory?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "Well, \"The Washington post\" three weeks ago had this investigation and they said that President Obama has now raised more money from Wall Street and the banks for this election cycle than all -- than all eight Republicans combined.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 683, "question": "Why are you taking this money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 684, "answer": "It's fascinating to find out why they're doing it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 695, "question": "I'm going to look you straight in the eye and say, Michael Moore, how many times have you been properly in love in your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 696, "answer": "Oh, my God.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Moore"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 708, "question": "Where are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 709, "answer": "Come on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 712, "question": "Properly in love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 713, "answer": "Be honest.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 720, "question": "How many time have you literally felt your heart in your gut?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 721, "answer": "Probably maybe two or three times.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 725, "question": "ORGAN: How does she put up with you charging around the world trying to put all of the world's problems to right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NNS", "TO", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 726, "answer": "Well, she -- in some ways, she's more aggressive than I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 727, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 728, "answer": "On some of these issues.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 730, "question": "What the hell's the breakfast table like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 731, "answer": "Well, we don't -- I don't -- we should eat breakfast.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 743, "question": "How many times have you been in love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 744, "answer": "It's irrelevant to this interview.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 764, "question": "How much do you feel you owe Martin Kindu Isaacs (ph), your husband now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 765, "answer": "I feel that I owe him my love.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Martin Kindu Isaacs"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111206pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 775, "question": "When you look at what happened to Amy Winehouse, do you think that could have been you if things had played out a different way for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 776, "answer": "I know -- I know it could have been me.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Amy Winehouse"]}}]